只要能救你，射多少次都可以
巴鲁苏，你真棒。
斯巴鲁君，回头见。
哇，姐姐，那是什么东西啊?  -太棒了..。
好爽啊
高潮 高潮
只要能救你，射多少次都可以
我的那里痒痒的。
内射我 内射我
我要，我要，全射给我吧，求你了
事实是我有点... ... 有点... ... 真的有点... ..。
我觉得怪怪的。
只要能救你，射多少次都可以
快掏出你的肉棒来
小穴被插满了 插满了
不要啊  高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
巴鲁斯，你是个懦夫吗？你真讨厌。
只要能救你，射多次都可以
让我们开始吧。（请懂二次元的翻译后面这句）
真的可以吗  来吧
会很舒服的
为了保护一个女人，从此就过着堕落的生活。
只要能救你，射多次都可以
你好! 斯巴鲁君，你总是来得这么突然。
最近，我穿越到这个世界，出现在我在乎的女人的面前
不知怎么的，我遇到了这个双胞胎女仆。
你怎么了？
你不想见到我？
啊... ... 不，不是那样，我很高兴。
你在骗我，斯巴鲁，我知道的。
我知道你不想说而已，我理解。
所以不要用谎言来欺骗我，你完全没没必要这么做。
不，我不是那个意思。
你姐姐呢？
姐姐? 我姐姐..。
为了得到魔法
首先，要让你的身体适应
的确如此
这样好舒服啊
这里？
好爽啊
怎么了? 你病了吗？
不，没有
事实上我只是有点... ... 有点... ... 有点。
我觉得很奇怪。
事实上,
当然,
我觉得我越来越热了。
接下来..。
这里
这里也是
然后,
就像以前一样。
我感觉比以前更舒服了。
这里
太棒了。
太神奇了。怎么会这样，太爽了
好舒服啊
你没事吧? 有什么我能帮忙的吗？
斯巴鲁君,
那个
我的胸部,
请摸我的胸部
你在说什么啊
我的乳头好痛。
这就是为什么... ... 请帮我揉揉胸部。
我不能做这样的事。
你就忍心看我着难受吗
我知道你不会见死不救的
我知道了
这里吗？
是的。
继续摸我
继续？
斯巴鲁君，求求你，继续... ..,
这样可以吗?
这边也要
你真的没事吗？
怎么回事啊。
斯巴鲁君,
请大胆的蹂躏我的身体
- 更大胆点?-是的。
等等。
-好舒服 -舒服吗? -是的。
用力点 在用力。
用力点?-是的。
So?
等等... 我再也受不了了。
斯巴鲁君-是的。
来直接的摸
我的胸部。
请尽情的蹂躏
直接？
-我的胸部好疼  -好的，好的，稍等一下。
把这个也脱了？
直接？
是的。
没错，就这是这样..。
继续..。
- 真的?-是的..。
-继续 继续。-我尽力在做啊。
你没事吧? 真的吗？
乳头
还是很疼
-乳头?-是的。
好痒。
等一下，那里... ，那里 -这里..。
- 你没事吧?-没事..。
摩擦乳头可能会好些。
继续
转动我的乳头
继续。
继续? 这点程度还不够。
除此之外，我还能做些什么呢？
吮吸我的胸部。
求求你了，斯巴鲁先生。
知道了。
我可以这样做吗? -可以。
好厉害。
我感觉好多了。
-继续舔。-好的。
那里! ..。
你确定你没事吗?-是的。
只有你能做到
太棒了。
接下来,
是这里了吗？
太棒了！
还有,
正如预期的小穴很舒服。
好舒服。
太棒了。
真不敢相信手淫这么爽。
好舒服。
继续 继续?-好的。
你确定你没事吗? -怎么了？
这里。
我怕痒。
斯巴鲁。
这里也要，求你了。
要不然我会痒死。
好的，好的，我能摸你这里吗?-可以。
求求你
这样？
太好了！
-用力 -用力？
像这样?-是的..。
Is this okay?
-Yeah, its good there.
这样可以吗?-可以，这样很舒服。
Please don’t stop.
-Don’t stop?
请不要停-不要停？
It’s painful. It’s painful?
I feel pain inside me.
我很痛苦。很痛苦? 我的小穴很痛苦。
Are you all right, really?
你真的没事吗？
I...
我..。
Now...
现在..。
Cant stand...
忍受不了了..。
I cant!
我不行了！
Inside me...
-W-wait!
- 我的里面...-等等！
Rem cant stand it anymore.
雷姆，再也受不了了。
W-wait!
等等！
I beg you, more.
求求你。
Feels good!
好舒服！
Awesome!
太棒了！
Not anymore!
果然不一样！
If your body is ready,
如果你的身体准备好了,
Next,
接下来,
The mana from his hard thing,
从硬物中吸取魔法
Prepare for penetration.
准备插入
Indeed.
的确如此。
Here I guess.
我想是这样吧。
Next...
接下来..。
Put inside the pussy.
放进小穴里。
Yeah, there.
是的。
There, more...
那里，继续 继续..。
I beg you.
求求你了。
Rem’s body’s is feeling weird.
雷姆的身体感觉怪怪的。
Subaru!
斯巴鲁！
What shalt we do? Subaru...
我们该怎么办? 斯巴鲁..。
Rem...
雷姆..。
Feels, weird.
感觉怪怪的。
Wait...
等等。
I need this,
我要这个
I want it.
You said we couldnt.
我想要，你说过我们不可以的。
But,
但是,
Its so painful.
太痛苦了。
I am feeling bad.
-S-silly!
-我感觉糟透了-傻瓜！
This is all I can think of.
我现在满脑子只有这个
Right here, subaru.
这个，斯巴鲁。
Its really hot.
真的很热。
Its very hard.
好硬。
Rems body is really hot, too.
雷姆的身体也非常热。
Wait a second.
-I beg you, subaru.
-等一下 -求你了，斯巴鲁。
Thats enough. Do as you please.
好吧 好吧，你想怎样就怎样
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Its big, subaru-kun.
好大啊，斯巴鲁君。
The inside of my body itches.
我的身体好痒。
Inside me in here.
这里好痒
Im tickling...
我在挠痒痒..。
Your thing, subaru...
肉棒，斯巴鲁..。
Can I put it inside me?
我能把它放进去吗？
Rem cant stand it anymore.
雷姆再也受不了了。
I am hot in here.
我这里很热。
I donut know why..
我也不知道为什么。
Can I do whatever I want?
我可以为所欲为吗？
It came in!
肉棒进来了！
I feel good inside.
插进去好舒服。
Hot and hard. Subaru.
又热又硬，斯巴鲁。
No!
不要！
Somehow I feel numb.
不知怎么的，麻酥酥的。
Subaru, this time, from behind.
斯巴鲁，这一次，从后面插。
Can I ask for it?
可以吗？
Subaru, you are reaching me deep inside.
斯巴鲁，你插的好深啊。
Feels good.
好舒服
More... Subaru, more I beg you!
继续... 斯巴鲁，求你了！
Lam...
我。
I will cum again... If youre so hard!
这么用力的话 我又要高潮了
Its amazing. My pussy...
太神奇了，小穴..。
More, please,
继续，求你了
No!
不要！
Subaru, more, I want more.
-More?
斯巴鲁，再来点，我还要 -还要？
Id like a little more, please.
我还要。
Here.
这里。
I feel so good.
好舒服。
Inside, inside me please.
操我  我操 。
It tickles inside. I beg you!
里面好痒，求你了！
Harder.
再用力点。
O!
啊！
Subaru you are so hard.
斯巴鲁，你真棒。
Its warm...
好暖和啊..。
Subaru-kun...
斯巴鲁君。
You did well.
你好厉害。
Is that it?
是这样吗？
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I feel much better.
我感觉好多了。
Thanks to you, subaru-kun.
多亏了你，斯巴鲁君。
To save you.
I’ll cum any number of times.
只要能救你，射多少次都可以
I‘ve been waiting for you, barusu.
我一直在等你，巴鲁苏。
You only did it for rem.
What is the meaning of that?
-你为什么只和雷姆做 -什么意思？
Only? What do you mean?
只有? 什么意思？
We had horns.
我们都有角。
But ever since the horns disappeared,
if we don’t replenish our mana.
但是自从角消失后，如果我们不补充我们的法力值。
We will get sick.
我们就会生病的。
No, lye been here many times.
I dont know what you’re talking about.
什么，我来过这么多次了，我不知道你在说什么。
There is not much else to say.
没什么好解释的。
You made rem get better with your thing.
你用肉棒治愈了雷姆。
Come to think of it, I remember a
memory like that from the past...
回想起来，我记得过去的一段记忆..。
Sister!
姐姐！
Here you go.
给你。
Rem! whats wrong with you?-Its painful...
-Are you okay? Can you stand?
雷姆! 你怎么了?-很痛...-你还好吗? 你能站起来吗？
Im here.
别怕，有我在
Sister, it hurts a lot.
姐姐，好痛啊。
Hold in there rem.
Youre gonna be okay with some treatment, okay?
等一下，你只要接受治疗就没事了？
You traveler, can you give us some mana?
你这个穿越者，你能给我们一些魔法力吗?
Huh? Mana?
啊? 魔法力
Yeah, hurry.
? 是的，快点。
Pull your cock out of there at once!
马上把你的老二掏出来
I cant do that!
! 我做不到！
It hurts!
-Rem?
-好痛!-雷姆？
Come on, come on! hurry up.
-Wait.
-快点，快点 -等等。
This way!
过来
You cant supply us with mana if you’re like this.
不硬起来的话 就没法获取魔力了
Rem, please wait a little longer.
雷，请再等一会儿。
Hurts...
好痛..。
Come on, do it right.
-What...
-快点，硬起来。-什么..。
Give me I beg you.
救我，求求你了。
Why is it not the same as before?
You’re such a worthless fellow.
为什么和以前不一样了? 你真是个没用的家伙。
Sister, hurry, I cant wait.
-Hold on, rem.
姐姐，快点，我快不行了 -等一下，雷姆。
It cant be helped.
真没办法
Its getting bigger.
-Im telling you, its amazing. Sister youre amazing.
-它越来越大了。-我教过你的，它太神奇了。姐姐，你太厉害了。
Now is the time to help this sloppy thing properly.
现在是时候正确地处理这件邋遢的事情了。
I beg you, let me swallow it.
我求求你，让我咽下去吧。
It’s really big.
真的很大。
But not yet. It stilt can get bigger, right?
还不够。它还可以变大，对吗?
Is it getting bigger? Awesome.
它变大了吗? 太棒了。
Big!
-More.
大一点! -还不够。
Now, please do your best for rem.
现在，请尽力帮助雷姆。
Sister...
姐姐..。
It hurts...
好痛..。
Its all right, rem.
没关系，雷姆。
Wi'll the mana make me healthy?
-Thats right.
-魔力真的会让我健康吗?  -没错。
So,
所以,
Rem do what I did. Just try it
雷姆，像我刚才做的那样，快试试
Yes.
好的
Right.
对。
Like this?
像这样？
Yeah, like that.
是的，就是这样。
Lick it with your tongue.
-Yes.
-用你的舌头舔它 -好的。
Perfect, rem.
-Really?
-很好，雷姆 -真的吗？
Maybe I am feeling a little better.
我感觉好点了。
Really?
-Yeah. But its still a little painful...
-真的吗? -是的，但还是有点疼..。
Come on, rem. You can do it.
-Yes, sister...
-加油，雷姆，你能做到的 -好的，姐姐..。
Big.
很大啊。
Are you all right, rem?
-Yes.
-你没事吧，雷姆? -没事。
This?
这个？
All right, put it in your mouth more.
没错，含深点。
Get plenty of mana, ok?
去获得足够的魔法力
The powerful mana is coming out.
强大的法力要出来了。
Now, you push and do your best.
-I beg you.
-现在，你用力，尽你最大的努力。-求求你了。
W-wait!
等等！
Very good, rem.
很好，雷姆。
Hurts...
好痛..。
Fighting.
加油。
Youre doing great.
你做得很好。
It’s gonna get better if you keep going.
-Yes.
- 如果你继续的话会好起来的 -是的。
Sister are you okay?
-I’m fine. Let’s keep going.
姐姐，你还好吗?-我很好，我们继续。
Give more power to rem.
-But.., You sister?
给雷姆 更多的能量。-但是，姐姐你... ，
I’m fine.
-But...
-我没事 -但是..。
If you dont get healthier,
如果你不能变得更健康,
Get all of it.
全吸出来来。
Yeah, like that.
是的，就像这样。
Sister, i’m fine now.
姐姐，我现在没事了。
You suck some more.
你再吸一点。
Hurry.
快点。
I...
我..。
You re have to get better.
-Thank you, rem.
-你得好起来 -谢谢你，雷姆。
Give more strength to my sister.
给我姐姐更多的能量。
Sister. Are you okay?-Its all right.
-111 Help you with my hand.
-姐姐，你没事吧? -没事。-我用手帮你拿着。
Are you okay?
-Yeah, it’s okay, it’s okay. Don’t worry about it.
-你还好吗? -是的，没事，没事，别担心。
Feelsgood.
好舒服
Oh, thats great.
I can feel the power of this thing.
哦，太好了。我能感觉到这东西的力量。
I can feel it. The power of this thing.
我能感觉到这东西的力量。
Give us more mana.
-I beg you.
-给我们更多的魔法力。-求求你。
There’s a lot of power inside it.
里面蕴含着巨大的力量。
Awesome!
太棒了！
Give me more please.
请再给我一点。
Give me more.
再给我点。
More.
还要
Give us more I beg you. The power of your thing.
给我们更多 我求求你，你那东西的力量。
It’s awkward.
虽然很尴尬
But I beg you to help us more.
但还是请你多帮帮我们。
More, I beg you, please.
再多一点，求求你。
Give me a lot of it.
多给我点。
I want a lot of mana.
我需要很多魔法。
Oh,i cum!
哦，要射了！
Wow, sister something came out.
-Wow, thats great.
哇，姐姐什么东西出来了。-哇，太棒了。
it's not coming out any more? Come we have to grab this
射不出来了吗?  别把这些浪费了
Oh, its amazing. Its overflowing with great power.
哦，太神奇了，充满了强大的力量。
It smells great.
-Yes.
闻起来真香-是啊。
So thick. Its such a waste.
好浓稠啊，真是浪费。
Awesome.
太棒了。
I’ve been in pain until now. I feel better.
现在终于好多了
I feel so much better.
我感觉好多了。
I dont know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
Do the same thing you did to rem.
-Eh?
就像你对雷姆做的那样
The same thing?
嗯? 同样的事？
Barusu. Did you see her bottom?
You are odious.
-巴鲁苏。你看到她的屁股了吗?  你真可恶
No, I am not.
不，我没有。
Are you serious?
You only think about women.
假正经，其实你一直在想着那方面
All right, just like I did to rem, okay?
好吧，那来吧，就像和雷姆那样？
You can start from the very beginning.
你可以从头开始。
Like this?
像这样？
Yeah.
是的。
Do the same thing you did to rem.
-The same thing?
-和我做同样的事情吧 -做同样的事？
Barusu, you can do it.
巴鲁苏，你可以的。
It’s...
这是..。
Not bad barusu, touch me more.
-More?..
不错吧，巴鲁苏，继续摸 - 继续吗。
Is this how it works?
-Yeah, you did this to rem, right.
-是这样的吗? -是的，你就是这样摸雷姆的吧。
Its really so sweet.
真是太棒了
Right on point, barusu.
正中要害，巴鲁苏。
you‘re usually a low-brainer But this must be your specialty.
-Ha? Whats that?
-你就是个低能废物，不过还算有这么个特长 -哈? 那是什么？
Barusu, how long do you intend to keep my clothes on
巴鲁苏，你打算把我的衣服穿
You plan to just do that?
你就打算只做到这点程度？
Come on.
来吧。
Pull down the zipper.
拉下拉链。
Just like you did to her.
就像你对她做的那样。
Like this?
像这样？
Youre good barusu. Very good.
好棒，巴鲁苏，非常好。
Lets do more.
让我们做更多点。
Now, barusu...
现在，巴鲁苏..。
How long are you just going to touch me over my clothe
你还要摸我的衣服摸多久
Touch it by yourself.
自己摸一摸。
You always practice this kind of stuff, don’t you?
-What are you talking about?
-你是不是经常这样摸? -你在说什么？
Do you want it like this?
这样你喜欢吗？
Oh, there.
哦，那儿。
Oh, good.
太好了。
Barusu, good. Yeah.
巴鲁苏，很好。
Thats it.
就是这样。
This?
这个？
Can I do this?
我可以这么做？
I love it in the nipples. Remember that.
我喜欢乳头有这样的，记好了。
This?
这个？
Feels good.
好舒服
Are you okay just touch barusu?
你就只会摸吗？
With rem.
和雷姆。
What else did you do?
- 你还做了什么
I sucked it.
我吸了。
Then start sucking.
那你开始吮吸吧
You always,
你总是...
Are you going to just touch my boobs?
你就回想摸我的胸吗？
So...
所以..。
Here comes.
我来了。
Hurry up.
快点。
Barusu, your tongue.
巴鲁苏，你的舌头。
Why are you so soft on it barusu?
为什么这么温柔，巴鲁苏？
This is really so sloppy.
这真是太草率了。
You sucked rems chest with your tongue?
-Thats right.
-你用舌头吮吸雷姆胸部? -没错。
Feels good!
好爽啊
Barusu....
巴鲁苏..。
If you suck it like that...
如果你像那样吸的话..。
Already?
这么快？
Barusu.,. Good.
巴鲁苏，很好。
I need you to suck me over here too.
这边也舔舔
Now this one.
现在是这个。
Where the hell do you think youre going?
你脑子里都在想些什么鬼
Youre such a pervert.
-V-you are wrong.
-这个变态。-你错了。
If you suck it like that,
如果你像那样吸,
Come on barusu,
拜托，巴鲁苏,
Here.
Do you keep on thinking about this thing?
这里，你是不是一直在想这件事？
Not really.
也不尽然。
If not,
如果没有,
We can forget about it.
算了
Do to me what you did with rem.
对我做你对雷姆做的事。
you touched this place with your dirty hands, didnt yol
你用你的脏手摸过这种地方吧
Right.
是的
Can I do this?
我能这么做吗？
Yeah, barusu.
是的，巴鲁苏。
Here?
这里？
Its a dirty hand gesture, barusu.
真下流，巴鲁苏。
Feels good.
好舒服
There.
-Here?
-那里-这里？
Do you like it here?
-Yeah, thats it.
-你喜欢这样吗? -是的，就是这里。
Feels good.
好舒服
Yeah, just keep going.
-Just like that?
是的，继续 -就这样？
You cant stop, okay?
-I know.
-别停，好吗? -我知道。
I feel good!
好爽
No!
不要
I came, I came, I came!
高潮 高潮了
In this stuff, youre quite good barusu.
在这方面，你TM是个人才
Come on.
来吧。
Next,
接下来,
Now.
现在。
Here.
这里
Now, do it like you did with rem.
现在，就像你对雷姆做的那样。
Can I suck it?
我能吸它吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah!
耶！
As fast as you can.
越快越好。
Lick it, lick it, lick it.
舔它，舔它，舔它。
Lick my pussy.
舔我的小学。
Smoothlike you did to rem.
Please.
就像你对待雷姆那样 拜托了。
I want you to suck my dripping wet pussy.
我要你吮吸我湿淋淋的小穴。
Make me feel good.
让我舒服
I feel good, barusu.
好棒，巴鲁苏。
Can I do this?
我能这么做吗？
Good. I feel very good!
很好，很舒服！
You are very skilled barusu!
你好擅长啊
Suck me where I feel best.
你找到我的敏感带了
No!
不要
I cant stand it anymore.
再也受不了了。
No, no, I came, I am gonna cum!
不，不，高潮 要高潮了
No!
不要
Cum!
高潮了
Feels good.
好舒服
Come on barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
Don’t stand there like a fool.
别像个傻瓜一样站在那里。
You need to lie down.
你躺下。
Here?
在这里?
Yeah, I want to do more.
是的，我想做更多。
What, barusu?
什么，巴鲁苏？
Did you get this hard when you sucked rems pussy?
你吸雷姆小穴的时候也这么硬吗？
Shut up!
闭嘴！
It’s really a dirty trick.
这真是个卑鄙的伎俩。
Its hot and its smelling awesome.
它很热，而且闻起来很棒。
Is this what you did in front of rem?
你在雷姆面前就是这么做的吗？
It doesn’t matter.
和你没关系。
What are you ashamed of?
你为什么感到羞耻？
Not much.
不是
Airight, lift up your ass.
好的，抬起你的屁股。
So this thing.
所以这个东西。
Should I suck it?
我可以吸它吗？
Its up to you.
这取决于你。
How on earth did rem sucked you like?
雷姆是怎么帮你吹的
I do not remember.
我不记得了。
look。。you dont remember because You have a little brain, barusu.
Indeed, cute little thing.
你就是个白痴，巴鲁苏。的确，可爱的小东西。
Do you want me to keep going? Barusu.
Your hips are moving.
- 你想让我继续吗?  你的屁股在动。
Because it’s so fast.
因为太快了。
Are you so happy that you can’t stand it? Barusu.
你这么高兴是不是太爽了。
Fair enough.
很公平啊
I cant stand it anymore.
我也受不了了。
You can put it inside my pussy.
你可以把它放进我的小穴
You know.
你知道怎么做吧。
When you fucked rem,
当你和雷姆做爱的时候,
You were all over the place, werent you?
你都插进去了，不是吗？
Coem on.
开始吧。
Can you see it?
你能看到吗？
Your mana, barusu.
你的法力
Stick it.
坚持住。
Awesome!
太棒了！
Im gradually getting bigger.
肉棒在变大
Are you all right, barusu?
你没事吧，巴鲁苏？
Awesome!
太棒了！
So good, barusu.
太棒了，巴鲁苏。
You are fucking my pussy.
小穴在摩擦。
Feels good!
好爽
Feels good, barus.
好舒服，巴鲁斯。
Your mana is such a violent thing.
你的魔力太惊人了
Awesome.
太棒了。
My stomach is full.
我现在满血状态
Inside me...
操我
Get in there.
Now,
现在,
I'll give you a good view, barusu.
好好的看吧，巴鲁苏。
How about it?
怎么样？
Your thing going inside my pussy?
Do you see it well?
肉棒在插入小穴? 你看得清楚吗？
Barusu...
巴鲁苏..。
If you move your waist like that...
如果你像那样移动你的腰..。
No!
不要
No way barusu, I am going to cum!
巴鲁苏，我高潮了！
No way! im coming. 1M coming! im coming!
不行，高潮了 高潮了 高潮了！
Its really hard.
好硬的肉棒
Is not over yet, barusu.
还没结束呢，巴鲁苏。
I‘ll Put inside like this.
像这样放进去。
Your thing is big and thick barusu.
你这肉棒又大又粗
Its all over inside my pussy.
全进去了。
Awesome!
太棒了！
Barusu!
巴鲁苏！
Feels good.
好舒服
Do like you did to rem.
就像你对雷姆做的那样。
Did she hit you like this?
她也是这样做的吗?
I feel good barusu!
好爽 巴鲁苏！
No, no, I will cum again.
不，不，我又要高潮了
I cum! I cum! I cum!
高潮 高潮 高潮了
Awesome.
太棒了。
Can you see it well, barusu?
你看得清楚吗，巴鲁苏？
Lets keep going until I fall asleep.
继续 继续
You like my pussy, dont you?
你喜欢我的小穴，对吧？
Come on, barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
Now,
现在,
Pound me from behind.
从后面猛插我。
Someone as incompetent as you barusu, be able to d
像你这样的屌丝人，也能做到的
Hurry barusu.
快点，巴鲁苏。
Do you know where it is?
你知道洞在哪儿吗？
Here.
这
I know
我知道
All right, barusu.
对 对，巴鲁苏。
Very good.
很好。
More deeper. Much more.
深一点 用力
Put it deeper.
再深入一点。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Your mana feels great.
你的魔法感觉棒极了。
Awesome!
太棒了！
Do it to me as much as you did to rem.
像对待雷姆一样对待我。
Thats awesome barusu.
太棒了，巴鲁苏。
You can still do it.
还能继续吧
Good barusu!
好棒，巴鲁苏!
No, I will cum.
Thats great! I will cum, barusu!
不要，我要高潮了。太棒了! 我要高潮了，巴鲁苏！
No more! I cum!
不要啊! 高潮了！
Feels good, barusu.
好舒服，巴鲁苏。
Thats right. That’s what I want.
没错，这就是我想要的。
I want you to fuck me as much as you want!
尽情的蹂躏我
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that’s it.
对 对 对 就是这样。
I will cum again.
我要再次高潮了。
I cum! I cum! I cum!
高潮 高潮 高潮了
No! I cum!
天啊 高潮了
It’s pretty good, barusu.
很不错，巴鲁苏。
Next up, in here.
下一站，是这里。
Get above.
上面点
Put it inside me.
插进去
Yeah.
是的。
I feel great, barusu.
好爽，巴鲁苏。
No, I cant think of anything except fucking
现在满脑子都是做爱
Barusu!, thats... I like that!
巴鲁苏 那样... ... 我好喜欢！
Not there!
不是那里！
I feel good, barusu.
好爽，巴鲁苏。
Im sorry for my incompetence. Barusu.
Do more! yes! more!
我为我的无能感到抱歉。巴鲁苏。继续操我 ! 对! 继续
No! I cum again!
I cum! I cum! I curn!
不行! 我又要高潮了! 高潮了! 高潮了! 高潮了！
Im coming. I cum!!
高潮了 高潮了！
Its not enough, barusu. I am still..
Can you still do it? More...
这还不够，巴鲁苏。我还要... ... 你还能做吗? 继续操我... ..。
Give me more.
再多给我点。
Yeah.
是的。
No...
不行..。
I cam already.
You can fuck me more.
我已经高潮了  在继续操死我
My pussy is making me a fool.
我的小穴太不争气了
No, I cum! I cum! I cum!
不，高潮了!高潮了! 高潮了！
Oh, I cum.
哦，高潮了。
No,..
不。
Barusu.
巴鲁斯
On this matter.
在这个问题上。
Honestly.
老实说。
Let me say,
我想说的是
Good job.
你很棒。
To save you.
I’ll um any number of times.
只要能救你，射多少次都可以
This time no matter where you are
i’ll protect you.
这次不管你在哪里，我都会保护你。
This is...
这是..。
Rem and ram in their childhood?
这是童年雷姆和拉姆？
Are you ready rem?
你准备好了吗？
Yes, sister.
是的，姐姐
Are you sure youre okay?
你确定你没事吗？
What are they doing?
他们在干什么？
Sister, what does it mean for us two to practice?
姐姐，我们两个练习对我们来说意味着什么？
We have to do this to replenish your mana.
我们必须这样做来补充你的法力。
But I rather go out to play outside.
但我更想出去外面玩。
You have to do this first,
or else do you want to die?
不这样做的话，你会死的
I get it.
我明白了。
So... Shall we?
那么... 我们...？
Yes.
是的。
Sister.
-Yes?
姐姐-怎么
It tickles somehow.
有点痒。
All right, leave it up to me.
没事的 交给我吧。
Yes.
好的。
But it feels weird.
但是感觉很奇怪。
Hang in there, be patient.
坚持住，忍耐会。
Its okay.
没事的。
Realty?
-Yes,
-真的吗 ?-是的,
Does it feel weird?
-Yes.
-感觉奇怪吗? -是的。
Do it soft.
温柔一点。
What the hell is this?
她们在搞什么鬼？
Somehow,
某种程度上
Its emt!...
（不懂）
Sister...
姐姐..。
I am feeling strange.
我感到很奇怪。
That’s fine.
没事的。
Re lax.
放松。
I feel stronger.
我感觉有效果了
But it’s not just this.
这样好不够
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Over here.
这边。
I feel strange.
我觉得很奇怪。
This, too,
这个也是,
This is how we will replenish our mana.
这就是我们补充法力的方法。
Yes.
是的。
But for some reason.
但出于某种原因。
My body.
我的身体。
Feels hot.
感觉很热。
Hot?
-Yes.
很热?-是的。
Thats it.
Really?-Yeah.
- 这就对了-真的吗 ?-是的。
Rems you feel very soft here.
你这里很柔软。
I’m embarrassed, sister.
我很害羞，姐姐。
It’s okay.
没事的。
Leave it to me.
交给我吧。
I get it.
我明白了。
I’m serious.
我是说真的
Rem, you hot in here too.
雷姆，你这里也很热。
My body... Is it weird?
我的身体... 很奇怪吗？
Its not strange.
这并不奇怪。
Everyone is like this.
每个人都是这样。
Is this normal?
这正常吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Rem,
雷姆,
Its all the same.
大家都一样。
Its normal to be this hard.
这里这么硬也是很正常的。
And...
还有..。
It really feels more strange.
真的感觉更奇怪了。
Now hang in there.
坚持住。
I can tell that you got harder in here.
我看得出来你在这里越来越硬了。
Why?
为什么？
It feels better and better.
You are getting ready.
因为越舒服，所以就越硬。
Somehow,
不知怎么的,
It tickles.
好痒。
Are you okay?
-I dont know.
你还好吗?-我不知道。
Then this one.
接下来
I’m ashamed.
好害羞啊。
Do not be ashamed.
Its just the two of us here, isn’t it?
别害羞，这里只有我们两个，不是吗？
Yes.
-You always take baths with me.
是的。-你总是和我一起洗澡。
But,
但是,
If you touch it...
如果你碰它..。
It’s getting harder.
-Here?-Yeah.
越来越硬了。-这里? -是的。
No, sister, its hot.
不要，姐姐，好热了。
Wait a little bit,
忍耐下
It’s really hard.
-Yes.
- 真的很硬 -是的。
Now, next,
接下来
Do you want to touch me?
-My sister?
-你想摸我吗? -摸姐姐？
Yes.
是的。
Come on.
来吧。
Here.
这里
Soft...
好柔软
Like this?
像这样？
Yeah.
是的。
Rems hands are so hot.
雷姆的手好烫。
Why is that?
为什么？
But youre hot, too.
但是你也很热了。
Because,
因为,
You are touching me right now.
你现在就在摸我。
Does it get hot when you touch it?
身体被摸就会变热吗
Yeah.
Right...
是的
Here?
这里？
Its really hard.
好硬。
There.
哪里...
Like this?
-Yeah.
-像这样? -是的。
Yes ram, there feels good.
是的，雷姆，好舒服。
Im glad.
我很高兴。
Just keep going.
-Yes.
- 继续 -好的。
Rem.
-Yes?
- 雷姆-什么事？
Me too.
我也想。
Touch me here.
被你摸
Yes.
是的。
Its hot, sister.
好热啊，姐姐。
Here?
Yeah
- 这里?-是的
Its super soft.
它超级柔软。
Like a little while ago
就想刚刚
Touch the tip.
抚摸乳头一样
Here?
-Yeah, there!
-这里? -对，那里！
Are you okay sister?
-Yeah its okay.
-你没事吧，姐姐? -是的，没事。
Rem you are so good. Good. Just like that.
你好会摸，很好 就是这样。
Feels good?
-Yes, very good.
-舒服吗? -是的，非常爽。
Does it hurt?
疼吗？
It doesnt hurt.
不痛。
Go on.
继续。
You’ve become very hard here.
-Ah rem!
-这里变得很硬了 -啊，雷姆！
No, fm so happy.
-Feels good?-I do.
-我很高兴。-舒服吗? -是的。
I‘m so happy when you touch me, rem.
你摸的好好爽
Im happy.
我很高兴。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
I'll make you feel good too.
我也会让你爽翻天
Its ok?
可以吗？
Sister.
姐姐。
Somehow I feel strange in the nipple.
不知怎么的，我的乳头有点奇怪。
Strange?
-Yes.
奇怪?-是的。
That’s what makes you feel good.
-Plesant?
-这样舒服吗。-很舒服？
Hot...
好热。
I'll make you feel great.
我会让你爽翻天的
Sister, I feel good.
姐姐，好爽
Its harder than before.
变得更硬了。
I feel good.
好舒服
Was it that good?
-Yes.
舒服吗?-是的。
Then,
然后,
Can you do the same for me?
-Yes.
-你能为我做同样的事吗?-是的。
Here?
-Yeah.
- 这里?-是的。
Rem youre skillful.
你很擅长啊
Rem. I feel good.
雷姆，好舒服啊
Here?
这里？
There.
-Here?
那里-这里？
No...
不行..。
Rems tongue is so hot too.
雷姆的舌头也很烫。
It got bigger.
它变得更大了。
Feels good.
好舒服
Feeling good, sister?
-Yeah,i feel good.
舒服吗，姐姐? -是的，很爽
Rem.
雷姆。
Its very hot.
好热啊
Sister.
姐姐。
Awesome.
太棒了。
I feel so good.
好舒服
I am getting hot down there for some reason.
-Below?
-不知道为什么我下面越来越热了 -下面？
Yeah
down where
-是的，-在哪里
Down below you konw
你知道的
Here.
这
And?
-Yeah, here.
是的，在这里。
Sister, its dirty to touch a place like that.
-Its okay, its not dirty.
姐姐，那里很脏的。-没关系，不脏。
Rem you are hot here,
你这里很热哦
It tickles here for some reason.
不知为什么，这里痒痒的。
It tickles?
-Thats the proof that you feel good.
痒吗 ?这就是你舒服的证明
Youre getting messy here, arent you?
-I don't know.
-你这里一塌糊涂了?-我不知道。
Rem,
雷姆,
Touch me here.
摸我这里。
Here?
-Yeah, there.
这里?-对，那里。
Its hot.
很热。
Sister, it’s hard here for some reason.
姐姐，不知道为什么这里又更硬了。
Your thing is hard too, rem.
你的东西也很硬，雷姆。
This is where you feet the best.
这是你舒服的地方
Rem, touch me more.
雷姆，继续摸啊
Sister, its weird there. It’s getting weird.
-It’s okay. It’s okay.
姐姐，这很奇怪，越来越奇怪了 -没事 没事的。
No. I feel too good.
不行啊，太舒服了。
I like it. I’m geeting hooked.
-No, sister, no, no. Its weird.
我喜欢这样。我已经上瘾了。-不行，姐姐，不，不。这很奇怪。
No more, I will cum.
不要啊，我要高潮了。
I cum!
高潮了
Are you all right, rem?
你还好吗，雷姆? ，
Somehow its gotten weird.
不知怎么的变得很奇怪。
I feel it here.
我这里很奇怪
Its because you feel good.
那是因为太舒服了
I'll make you feel good, rem.
我会让你更爽的，雷姆。
Lie down here.
躺在这里。
Yes.
是的。
Sister, what are you doing?
姐姐，你要做什么？
You have to learn this.
你必须学会这一点。
Get your butt up.
站起来。
Im ashamed.
好害羞
You have to do this right..
-I get it.
你必须这么做. .-我明白了。
Spread your legs.
张开你的腿。
I’m embarrassed, sister.
-It’s all right.
-好害羞，姐姐 -没事的。
It‘s just us two here.
-But...
-不用害羞，又没别人 -但是..。
Its okay. Come on.
没事的，来吧。
Can i?
可以吗？
Sister, do not do that.
姐姐，不要这样做。
Thats impossible.
不行哦
Sister!
姐姐！
Rem you are not dirty in here.
你这里很干净哦。
It’s very delicious.
-Is it delicious?
好美味。-美味吗?
Compared to earlier.
与之前相比
Something is weird.
变得更奇怪了。
Sister, I feel good.
姐姐，好舒服
Its all right, rem.
没事的，雷姆。
This is weird.
这太奇怪了。
If you do it so fast.
如果你做得这么快话
It feels weird.
会感觉怪怪的。
It’s okay, even though it became weird, you got hard.
没事的，即使变得很奇怪，这里还是硬了。
You... Sister dont!
姐姐 不要啊！
Sister.
姐姐。
Sister, I feel weird.
姐姐，我觉得怪怪的。
Its all right, rem.
没事的，雷姆。
Its not over yet.
还没有结束。
What are you gonna do?
你打算做什么？
Stay where you are.
呆在原地别动。
Lets get together.
让我们一起
There.
这里
Sister! it’s hot!
姐姐，好烫！
Its getting really hot.
越来越热了
Sister I feel horny.
姐姐，我很饥渴。
Rem, youre also getting wet.
雷姆，你也湿答答的了。
Sister, I feel good.
姐姐，好舒服
Feels good.
感觉不错。
No!
-Rem!
不!-雷姆！
Sister.
姐姐。
No way I feelso good.
不要  好爽啊
I can’t stop.
-Stop it. It’s getting weird.
- 我停不下来 -停下来，越来越奇怪了。
It’s okay, rem. You can be weird as you please.
没事的，雷姆，尽情享受吧
Sister, it’s so wet.
姐姐，这么湿了。
Me too.
我也是。
Rem.
雷姆。
Now, rem.. Do it by yourself.
现在，雷姆... 你自己动起来。
Touch your chest.
摸摸你的胸部。
Feels good.
-Yeah, rub it and enjoy it.
- 好舒服 -是啊，揉搓它，尽情享受。
This feels great, sister.
-I feel great, too.
-好爽，姐姐 -我也是。
Feels good.
好舒服
You’re working so hard.
-Its good, rem.
-你真棒 -好舒服，雷姆。
Feels good!
好爽
I will cum!
高潮了
Sister.
-Yes?
- 姐姐-怎么了？
But this..
但是这个..。
If we fornicate,
如果我们百合的话
Isnt it meaningless?
这不是毫无意义吗？
Rem.
雷姆。
I‘m  afraid I will get weird.
我怕我会变得古怪。
I c-cum...
要射了 要射了
Damn it!
该死！
To save you.
I’ll um any number of times.
只要能救你，设多少次都可以
When will I be able to go to emilia?
我什么时候能去艾米莉亚？
Wait a minute!
why do you always show up in front of me?
等一下！为什么你们总是在我面前出现？
It’s fate. For me to... No...
Its to make us feel good.
这就是命运 对我来说... ... 不... ... 这是为了让我们舒服。
Subaru-kun.
斯巴鲁君。
Lets start from here...
From one... Eh no... From ero.(Zero)
让我们从这里开始... 从一开始... 不... 从零开始。(零)
Now, barusu, lie down.
现在，巴鲁苏，躺下。
Give us a lot of mana today.
今天要给我们很多魔力。
Give us a lot, please.
请多给我们一些。
Subaru-kun.
斯巴鲁君。
Welt. Do as you please.
好吧，随你的便吧。
Whats wrong, barusu?
怎么了，巴鲁苏？
Are you nervous?
你紧张吗?
Your body is getting hot.
你的身体越来越热了。
Its so very hot.
太热了。
Rem,
雷姆,
Look at this.
看看这个。
Yes.
好的。
Come on, barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
I guess you like this too.
我知道你也很喜欢的
You look like a girl in here.
你这里看起来就像个娘们
I know its hardened.
我知道它变硬了。
Stop it.
别说了。
Subaru-kun.
斯巴鲁君。
Down here.
在这下面。
Its very hard.
很硬哦
I cant stand it.
我受不了了。
More.
继续
Well barusu, we barely touched you a little,
and you’re that hard already?
巴鲁苏，我们只是轻轻碰了你一下，你就这么硬了？
Hot...
好热啊。
Do you feel good?
舒服吗？
Now over here, too.
这边也要
Here.
这里
Its harder than before.
比以前更硬了。
Its really hard.
真的很硬
How about this one, barusu?
尝尝这个，巴鲁苏？
Your thing in trembling.
肉棒在颤抖。
Subaru, I'll do this one.
斯巴鲁，我来舔这边
It’s alright, you can moan.
没事的，你可以呻吟。
You make those dirty sounds? Barusu.
是你发出那些肮脏的声音的吗? 巴鲁苏。
Feeling great, arent you?
很舒服吧
Say something cute. Please.
尽情享受吧
Awesome.
太棒了。
It has became so hard.
变得这么硬
Then I'll enjoy this meal.
那我就好好享用这个肉棒
Its really hard.
真的很硬。
It’s fully hard.
太硬了。
Right here, subaru.
这里，斯巴鲁。
I will rub you up and down.
上下的蹂躏你懂的乳头
what’s realty going inside your brain barusu? Youre quite
-Shut up.
你的脑子里到底在想什么呢，巴鲁苏? 你真是个LSP -闭嘴。
You are holding out a lot.
Youre flinching.
你很会忍耐啊  有点畏缩了吧
Its tingling in here.
这里有点刺痛吧
Are you feeling that good?
舒服吗
I will make you feel even better.
我会让你更舒服的哦
The sound of rems sucking you is pretty great, right?
雷姆给你吹的声音很棒吧
Enjoy it well and cum a lot.
尽情的享受吧，然后全射出来
Subaru, your thing is delicious.
斯巴鲁，你的肉棒真好吃。
Would you like it deeper?
你想再深一点吗？
Speaking of that, barusu.
说到这个，巴鲁苏。
Feels you got harder than usual.
感觉你这比平时更硬了。
Is this good enough to justify such a boner?
看来足以证明你很爽啊？
Youre good here, dont you?
这里很舒服吧？
How do you feel, mr. Subaru?
感觉如何，斯巴鲁先生？
You cant stand it because we do
you up and down, right barusu?
受不了我们姐妹双管齐下吧
Pretending to be innocent, right barusu?
u? 一脸无辜的样子
Kinda cute.
还真是有点可爱。
Are you feeling that good? Barusu?
舒服吗? 巴鲁苏？
You look like a tuna barusu.
你看起来像条金枪鱼。
Served like a food, aren't you?
像食物一样被端上来，不是吗？
Make us feel good, too.
该让我们舒服了。
Rem.
-Yes?
- 雷姆-什么事？
Sister, thank you.
姐姐，谢谢你。
Come on, barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
You know what to do, dont you?
你不是知道该怎么做
I know.
我知道。
Feels good.
好爽
Is it smooth? Subaru-kun
光滑吗? 斯巴鲁君
Its smooth.
-No, barusu.
-滑溜溜的 -不行，巴鲁苏。
Here?
这里？
Yeah, yeah.
是的，是的。
You’ve improved a bit. I feel great.
你有进步，我感觉好爽。
Barusu.
L envy you.
好羡慕你啊
I feel so great!
屌爆了
You look very happy.
你看起来很高兴。
Sister.
姐姐。
I feel good.
好爽
Do you feel good? Subaru.
舒服吗? 斯巴鲁。
Hes licking you a lot.
-I feel good
-已经舔了很久了 -好舒服
All right, barusu.
好吧，巴鲁苏。
Subaru.
斯巴鲁。
I... Want to get touched.
我也想要被抚摸。
Please.
求你了。
My body feels different,
我的身体感觉变了
Now, barusu, like you just did.
Make sure rem feels good too.
现在，巴鲁苏，就像你刚才做的，也让雷姆舒服起来
I am happy.
我很快乐。
Feels good.
好爽
Great... I feel great there.
很好... 好爽
Yes, please. Touch me more.
是的，请多摸摸我。
Here?
-Yeah, I feel good.
-这里? -是的，好舒服
You look happy.
你看起来很开心。
Rem’s nipples are so hard.
雷的乳头太硬了。
Barusu, you are excited, too.
Lets enjoy more.
巴鲁苏，你也兴奋了吧。让我们在舒服点
Re lly...
是的
Im glad its got hard.
我很高兴它变得硬了。
It’s very soft
它非常柔软，
I feel like it’s going to burst.
我感觉它就要爆炸了。
Its very hard.
好硬
Awesome.
太棒了。
Really.
Rem looks so happy.
-I feel so great.
-雷看起来很开心 -我感觉好舒服。
Barusu.
Lets rub other places too.
Where?
-该换个地方。-哪里？
Down and down.
下面
Rem and rams.
雷姆和拉姆的小穴。
Pussy. You don't know if I don't tell you?
-I know.
-难道我没告诉你吗 ?-我知道了。
I want you to touch me there.
我要你摸我的那里。
Hurry.
-I get it.
-快点-我知道了。
Barusu, here.
巴鲁苏，这里。
Touch the two of us.
触摸我们两个的。
Subaru...
斯巴鲁..。
All right, barusu.
对 对，巴鲁苏。
Hey, barusu, you hear me?
My pussy is already soaked.
嘿，巴鲁苏，你听到了吗?  我的小穴已经湿透了。
I feel good.
好爽
Awesome.
More, I beg you.
太棒了，求你在继续
Can I do this?
-I feel good.
我能做这个吗?-我感觉很好。
Barusu!
巴鲁苏！
Feels good.
好舒服
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Oh, awesome barusu.
I feel good.
棒极了，巴鲁苏，很舒服。
It’s kind of tingling.
有点刺痛。
Wait.., This is good!
等等，很舒服
I'm coming. I will cum! no way.
1‘m coming. Im coming!
高潮了  高潮了  高潮了  高潮了
Feels good, barusu.
好爽啊，巴鲁苏。
Barusu your mana.
你的法力。
You must be impatient.
你一定是不耐烦了吧。
Its hard.
这很硬哦。
Rem.
-Yes.
- 雷姆 -是的。
Do you want to?
想要吗？
Subarus mana...
伊巴鲁斯 · 马纳。
I want it.
我想要。
Come on barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
Rem is asking you.
雷在向你请求。
Is that okay?
可以吗？
Yes.
是的。
Now rem, lie down there,
雷姆，躺在那里,
Yes, sister.
好的 姐姐。
Come on, barusu.
来吧，巴鲁苏。
Is it ok? With your mana.
可以吗? 用你的魔力。
You can make rem feel good.
你可以让雷姆舒服的
Big...
好大啊
Subaru..
斯巴鲁。
Give me a lot.
请给我
Your mana.
你的法力。
Amazing! it makes me full!
太神奇了，插满了
I am full!
插的满满的
Come on barusu, make sure she loves it.
-I know.
拜托，巴鲁苏，一定要让她高兴 -我知道。
Give me more I beg you!
继续 继续，求求你！
Here?
-Yes!
这里?-是的！
I feel good!
好舒服
More.
-Harder?-Yes...
-继续。-用力? -好的..。
I like it harder.
用力操我
Youre very erotic, barusu.
Lets do more.
你很淫荡哦，巴鲁苏。让我们做更多些
I think I wilt burst!
我想我会崩溃的！
I want more.
Its not enough yet?-I get it...
-我想要更多。这还不够吗? -我明白了..。
But subaru...
但是 斯巴鲁..。
Are you feeling good inside me?
-Yeah,i feel good.
我的小穴舒服吗? -是的，我感觉良好。
Feel free to do it.
尽情操死我
No way!
不行了
Thats it, barusu. More intense.
就是这样，巴鲁苏，再强烈一点。
I feel great.
屌爆了
I want more of subaru's stuff.
给我 我还要更多
Barusu.
Awesome.
太棒了。
Your buried your mana inside her.
你把你的魔法注入她体内了
Smelts nasty.
闻起来下流啊
...Subarus mana.
... 斯巴鲁的魔力
Barusu.
I cant take it anymore.
我再也受不了了。
Barusu put your mana in here.
巴鲁苏 插进来
Thats great, barusu.
太棒了，巴鲁苏。
I am full.
插满了小穴。
Sister, looks like you enjoying it a lot.
-I feel good.
姐姐，看起来你很啥服务啊 -好舒服啊
Barusu..
巴鲁苏。
Its very hard.
好硬的肉棒
Feels good.
好棒
Give me more. Barusu give me your mana!
再给我点，巴鲁苏，给我你的法力！
Feels good.
好爽
Its great. Its rubbing inside my pussy. Its amazing.
太棒了。肉棒在摩擦小穴。太美妙了。
Yeah, fuck me more,
继续操我啊
No, no, no, no! feels so good.
-I feel hot again.
不行 不要啊 ! 舒服死了。-好舒服
I feel good. I feel good.
No, that’s too intense barusu!
好爽，好爽 不要啊，太激烈了
No, I will cum. I cum
高潮 高潮了
I cum! I cum!
Awesome.
太棒了。
Feels good.
好舒服
If you pump like that...
这样抽插的话
I feet great, barusu.
我会很舒服的，巴鲁苏。
Yeah, fuck me more!
对 对  继续操死我
I want more...
我还要
No, barusu!.
Do it as intense as you did to rem. Yeah.
不够，巴鲁苏! 。要像你对待雷姆一样激烈程度。
That’s it.
Oh, no, I am gonna cum again!
就是这样，不，我又要射了！
Awesome.
太棒了。
Barusu.
Awesome.
太棒了。
My pussy has become very wet.
我的下面都湿透了。
I envy you for hard that was.
我真羡慕你啊
Rem wants more of that too.
雷姆也想要更多。
Its wet again.
又湿了。
I will do it.
让我给你吹
Barusu do you want to put it inside
remus pussy again? I will help you.
还想插雷姆的小穴吗
Can you do more?
可以操我吗
Do you feel all right?
可以吗
Rem’s so wet here.
雷姆的这里已经湿透了
Barusu, you look pretty distressed.
巴鲁苏，你看起来很痛苦。
Do you feel good?
舒服吗
Its making me full inside.
插满小穴了
Your inside rem.
Its getting bigger.
插入小穴了   肉棒在变大
I feel good. I feel good!
好爽 好舒服啊
Barusu youre good.
巴鲁苏，你真厉害
Is it that good?
-I cant stop my back.
舒服吗? -我停不下来了
All right, rem.
-Can I feel even better?
-对 对，雷姆 -可以让我更舒服吗？
No way!
不行啊
Awesome.
太棒了。
No!
He‘s trembling a lot.
他抖得很厉害。
Its amazing. Its tingling inside me.
太美妙了，肉棒插入我的体内
My wet pussy.
小穴都湿了
But, it’s stilt not enough.
但是，这还不够。
But rem.
-Yes?
-雷姆 -什么？
Next...
接下来..。
Its my turn.
轮到我了。
Can I watch it form up close?
-Fine.
-我能近距离观察一下吗? -可以。
Barusu.
Inside...
进去了
Thats great, barusu.
-My pussy.
-好爽，巴鲁苏 -我的小穴。
Its wet here. Touch me a lot please.
湿透了，请多摸摸我。
Hey, barusu, can you hear me?
My vagina is so wet when you fucked it hard.
嘿，巴鲁苏，你能听到我说话吗? 当你用力操我的时候，我的阴道都湿透了。
Feels good!
好爽
No, no way.
不行 不要
Its hard. If you poke it like that...
-Its very hard.
-好硬，如果你这样戳的话... -好硬啊。
I can’t!
不行了
I cant stand it. I feel good!
我受不了了，太舒服了
After that, fuck me too.
-Wait!
-待会也继续操我 -等等！
Barusu, I cum!!
巴鲁苏，我高潮了! ！
No, no!!
不要
I feel so good.
好舒服
Sister.
姐姐。
Thats great, barusu.
太棒了，巴鲁苏。
Its amazing. My waist shakes.
Its so wet.
太不可思议了。我的腰晃。好湿了。
It smells erotic.
闻起来很淫荡
Feels good.
好爽
I envy you.
我羡慕你。
Barusu, great...
巴鲁苏，好爽
No, no...
No, its not. Its trembling inside.
It’s so good, I will cum again.
肉棒在小穴抽插。好舒服  又要高潮了
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Cum!!
高潮了
Awesome.
太棒了。
I feel really weird inside.
小穴变得很奇怪
Rem’s wetness.
雷姆湿润了
And my wetness.
我的也湿润了。
Barusu, its amazing.
太棒了。
Its a dirty smell yet very sexy.
这是一种下流的气味，但是非常性感。
I...
我..。
I want the same as my sister.
我想要和我姐姐一样的。
Fuck me a lot from behind, please subaru.
从后面干我，拜托你。
Its amazing.
太神奇了。
Is it good from behind barusu?
-I feel good.
-后入式舒服吧?-很舒服。
Theres a lot going on there.
那里在不停抽插
My pussy, feels great!
小穴好舒服 好舒服！
Barusu youre doing great.
巴鲁苏，你做得很好。
Ifm going crazy!
-Nice movement barusu.
-我要疯了! -腰技不错，巴鲁苏。
No!
不！
Barusu youre amazing, keep going like that.
巴鲁苏，你太棒了，继续保持这样。
My pussy feels amazing!
小穴好舒服
Cuml. I will cum again!
高潮 又要高潮了
I think I will die.
我想我会死的。
Its very intense, barusu.
非常强烈，巴鲁苏。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Its so intense. I feel weird.
太激烈了，我感觉怪怪的。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Youve become very hard again. Barusu.
肉棒又硬了
Feels good.
好舒服
But barusu, im going to use this more.
但是，巴鲁苏，我会好好利用的
In my pussy this feels so good.
操我的时候真的很舒服
Here you go, barusu.
Do it.
来吧，巴鲁苏，快点。
My sister is so stubborn.
我姐姐很执着的
Fuck my pussy a lot.
操死我的小穴
Barusu you make me feel so good.
巴鲁苏，让我舒服
Hurts.
很疼。
It’s hard again, barusu.
又硬了，巴鲁苏。
Does she feel good inside?
里面舒服吗
I'll make you feel good here, too.
我来让你舒服点
Barusu, I feel good!
巴鲁苏，我感觉好极了！
Do it more. More. More!
-Its really erotic, I can see everything from there.
再做一点，再做一点，再做一点!-这真的很下流，我看的一清二楚
That feels really good, barusu.
感觉真棒，巴鲁苏。
I feel so good and weird.
屌爆了
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Thats good, barusu... Barusu!
很好，巴鲁苏... ... 巴鲁苏！
No, not that!
不，不是那个！
No, no...
不不。
I cum! cum! cum! cum!
高潮  高潮了
Are you going to do more?
-I can.
- 还要吗? -我要。
Barusu, this is not enough.
巴鲁苏，这还不够。
More... A little more...
继续 继续
More please.
请继续操我
Thats great, barusu.
太棒了，巴鲁苏。
I feel good.
很舒服
It’s all over the place.
全插进去了
Barusu.
-It’s so big, mr. Subaru.
-巴鲁苏 -好大啊，斯巴鲁先生。
Yeah, fuck my pussy more.
操我 操我 操死我
Awesome!
太棒了！
It makes me so full!
小穴被插满了
No, I cum, I cum again.
天啊 要高潮了  又要高潮了
I came. No way! I curn! I cum!
-I will cum!
-高潮了 高潮了 高潮了 高潮了 -射了
No, barusu, you’re still cumming.
Release it inside.
不行，巴鲁苏，你还在射，把它放进去。
Now, I will squeeze you with my pussy.
现在，小穴要夹紧肉棒
My sister's pussy...
我姐姐的小穴..。
You look distressed, barusu.
You released it all?
你看起来很沮丧，都射出来了吧？
You came?
你射了？
If you get squeeze me like that...
如果你像那样挤我..。
Oh, its coming out.
哦，都出来了。
Almost...
You came? Barusu.
- 差点... 射了吧?
Awesome.
太棒了。
It’s all over the place.
里面全是啊
Its very strong.
好浓稠
Barusu, you came inside me.
巴鲁苏，中出我了
It smells so strong.
闻起来很浓。
But barusu,
但是巴鲁苏,
Can you still keep going?
你还能继续吗？
Thats too much, sister.
那太多了，姐姐
I want to... I want to do it too.
我想... 我也想这么做。
Can you do it?
你能做到吗？
Subaru.
斯巴鲁。
Do it to rem, too.
请操我
Like you did with my sister,
就像你操我姐姐那样,
I want a lot.
我要更多的
I want a lot of it.
我要更多
Come on barusu, rem is begging you.
-I beg you!
拜托，巴鲁苏，雷姆求你了-我求你了！
Make me feel good please!
让我舒服
I feel good!
好爽
Please, more!
拜托，继续
Come on barusu, do it more.
Do it harder.
加油，巴鲁苏，再加把劲，再加把劲。
Inside my pussy, please!
操小穴 使劲操，求你了！
What’s wrong, barusu?
怎么了，巴鲁苏？
You can’t stand it?
你受不了了？
Give me a lot please!!
请给我很多! ！
Subaru, my pussy...
斯巴鲁，我的小穴..。
I beg you.
我求你了。
Im so wet.
我湿透了。
Its very big.
它非常大。
What a noise.
真吵。
Please give me a lot!
请给我很多！
Now, give her a lot of it.
现在，射给她把
I want a lot of stuff inside me.
请把魔力注入我体内
Give me a lot, please!
请多给我一点！
Oh, I will cum...
哦，我要射了..。
It feels hot.
好烫。
Thats great, barusu,
太好了，巴鲁苏,
Im glad you came a tot inside me.
谢谢你注入那么多魔力给我
Barusu I will clean you up.
巴鲁苏，我帮你弄干净
Me...
我..。
I wont leave a drop.
我不会浪费一滴魔力。
Barusu, good work.
巴鲁苏，干得好。
See you again, mr. Subaru.
再见，斯巴鲁先生。
嘿，你为什么生下我? ，妈妈..。